

INFO

Nationality: Pakistani Status: Single Date Of Birth: 08-Nov-1996 Religion: Islam

Place Of Birth: Sialkot - Pakistan. Address:

Model Town, Market Road, Sialkot Paksitan.

- +92-334-488-5050
- zianejaz@gmail.com
- zianejaz.github.io/portfolio

PROFILE

I am 23 years old MERN/ Full Stack web developer from Sialkot Pakistan. As a freelancer I have gained experience using python/JavaScript to develop user-friendly, interactive web apps. I love working with people, especially if they have the same passion, I have for what they do.

QUALIFICATIONS

Completed

O Level Cambridge University. A Levels Cambridge University. Intermediate Gujranwala board. CS50 Harvard University through EDX.

Ongoing/ Future Plans

AWS Developer: Building on CS50's Web Programming with Python and JavaScript. Mobile development

using React Native

HOBBIES & INTERESTS



TOOLS



ZIAN EJAZ Full Stack Web Developer

SKILLS

DESIGN



FRONT-END











BACK-END













EXPERIENCE

MARKETING EXECUTIVE at QS PAKISTAN from November 2012 to April 2013.

COSTUMER SERVICES EXECUTIVE at GERRY'S FEDEX VISA DEPARTMENT from January 2015 to APRIL 2016.

Graphic Designer and Web Developer at THE GRACE PRODUCTS from APRIL 2016 to MARCH 2018

Web Developer at **WOO SOFTWARE** from JUNE 2018 to APRIL 2020

CONNECT



https://www.linkedin.com/in/zianejaz/



https://github.com/zianejaz



https://zianejaz.github.io/portfolio